Nguyen Tuong Duy



64 Binh Quoi Street
Binh Thanh District
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

E-mail: duy.pateo@gmail.com

Website: http://duypateo.github.io

Phone: (+84) 165 4265 303

SUMMARY

I'm Duy and I'm a Developer. I have experience with Web developement technologies. Programing language is only the tools and the most important thing is programing logic thinking and problem solving skills that I want to improve in my career opportunities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FHH STARTUP January 2017 - December 2017

Front End Developer

Description:

- Building Customer website frontend
- Building Landing page builder web app front end (https://fhhpage.com/)

Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Python Flask
- Jinja template
- GIT (Bitbucket)
- Foundation Framework
- Boostrap Framework

timviecnhanh.com January 2018 - January 2018

HTML, CSS Freelancer

Description:

■ Code HTML CSS from PSD template

Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS

OPPO Vietnam March 2018 - July 2018

Backend Developer

Description:

Nouven Tuong Duy

- Develope ERP System with Team
- Create websites for Marketing Campaign
- Research and build mobile application from Website technologies.

Technologies:

- PHP
- Zend PHP Framework
- Phalcon PHP Framework
- Apache Cordova

EDUCATION

Information Technology

Ho Chi Minh University of Transport

Skills:

- C++
- C#
- Java
- Mobile Programing
- HTML/CSS/JS
- PHP

INTERESTS

- Listen to Music
- Watching Movies
- Reading
- Photography
- Travel
- Running

LANGUAGE

- Vietnamese (Native)
- English (Basic Comunication)
- Chinese (Beginer)

September 2014 - July 2018

giiven Tuong Diiv